WALID RAMADAN

RAS Al-Khaimah · 0545423730 WALID.RAMADAN80@GMAIL.COM

Performance-driven with 10 years of experience selling in dynamic and fast-paced environments. Proven experience mixed with passion and dedication needed to drive new business leads through implementation of a fully integrated sales strategy. Committed to working with sense of urgency to meet and exceed territory sales goals. Adaptable and flexible to accommodate growing customer needs and requests

EXPERIENCE

01/10/2018 - PRESENT

SALES EXECUTIVE, AL YOUSUF MOTORS - YAMAHA

- -Achieve and maintain the company prescribed standard sales policies and procedures thereby ensuring maximum customer satisfaction and repeat sales.
- -Analyze market situation and identify and services.
- -Explore opportunities to sell products and services.
- -Achieve allocated monthly sales target.
- I got trophy employ of the month DEC 2023
- -My efforts culminated in obtaining the best employee of the year 2023.

7/2011-8/2018

SALES EXECUTIVE, MANSOUR AUTOMOTIVE - CHEVROLET

- -Improved sales by managing sales lifecycle from lead generation through contract negotiations and closings
- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales.
- Conducted on-site product demonstrations to highlight features, answer customer questions and redirect concerns toward positive aspects.
- Cultivated lasting rapport with key industry clients by providing accurate pricing and credit terms to meet customer objectives.

1/2009-6/2011

Sales Executive, AL LEITHY – USED CARS

- Meet clients and show them products.
- Close deals and offer more services.
- Achieve or exceed the allocated monthly sales target

EDUCATION

INSTITUTE OF QUALITATIVE STUDIES, TOURISM STUDIES

SKILLS

- Worked in a team-oriented, collaborative environment
- Ability to work under pressure
- -Time management

- Analytical and problem-solving skills
- Willing to relocate and accept responsibility
- Communication and report writing